Okay, so what's the next step?
那么，下一步是什么？
This is the most common subject line
在看了我先前的5个视频的人所发给我的数百封邮件中，
in the hundreds of emails that I receive from people who have watched the first five videos
这个是最常见的主题，
in the 'Teachings of Jesus' playlist.
在这个“耶稣的教导”的列表里。
They've seen the need to forsake all in obedience to Jesus
他们已经看到了在顺从耶稣的事情上，撇下所有的重要性。
but they all imagine that they'll be left standing on the side of the road
但是他们都在想像之后他们会被扔在路边，
with only the clothes on their backs, when it's all over, slowly starving to death and dying for lack of medicines.
只有他们的衣服在背后，这就完了，只能慢慢的死于饥饿，或者死于疾病，
Freezing from the cold.
或者死于寒冷。
Or facing some other miserable existence that will ultimately kill them and all their family.
或者是面对一些可悲的状况，导致最终会毁了他们和他们的家庭。
The most common assumption is that the next step is to head off into the wild
最常见的假想中的下一步，是向着旷野前进
foraging for food and maybe eventually finding a little plot of ground in the mountains
去寻找食物，或许最终能在山上找到一小块地，
where they can grow their own food until Jesus returns.
在那里，他们可以种些食物自己吃，直到耶稣回来。
Now, the idea of dying, whether through starvation, the cold, or some illness, is probably not a bad one
现在，这个关于死亡的想法，无论是饿死，是冻死，或是病死，或许不是个坏想法，
because it forces us to face the ultimate consequence of living by faith in Jesus.
因为那会强迫我们面对最终极的结果：在基督里靠信心永远活着。
He says, "Take up your cross, and follow me."
他说，“背起你的十字架来跟随我。”
Until we get it into our heads that God is allowed to let us die
我们的头脑要明白，除非上帝许可我们死，
we are not really going to be ready for what is next.
我们不会真的死掉，下一步不会就绪。
Some of the excuses that people come up with for not obeying Jesus when he says to leave it all behind
有一些借口，在人们准备不顺从耶稣的话时被使用，他们说从永恒的角度来看，
can be pretty pathetic in the light of eternity.
撇下一切是一个非常没有价值的事情。
I have to ask myself, "Do these people believe there's a God at all?"
我必须得问我自己，“这些人是真相信有一位上帝吗？”
"Can't they see that he has the right to tell them to leave it all?"
“他们看不到他有着让他们撇下一切的权力吗？”
"And can't they see, that he has the power to provide whatever he thinks they need?"
“他们看不到他有能力提供一切他认为他们需要的吗？”
"So why are they making excuses?"
“所以他们为什么找借口？”
Nevertheless, the answer as to what is next
不管怎样，这个答案就像“下一步是什么”一样，
should be right there in our subconscious from the moment that we hear Jesus speaking to us and saying
当我们听到耶稣教导我们时，在我们的潜意识里出现，
"Leave it all for me."
当耶稣说“为我撇下一切”时。
At the end of Matthew's gospel, and at the end of Mark's gospel, are verses which had been referred to as
在马太福音的最后，还有在马可福音的最后，是一些被我们称为：
the Great Commission.
大使命，的经文。
They say, "Go into all the world, and preach the good news, to everyone."
那里说，“你们往普天下去，传福音给万民听”。
Matthew's version adds these words
在马太福音里添加了这些话：
"Teaching them to obey everything that I have told you to do."
凡我所吩咐你们的，都教训他们遵守，
So, imagine yourself sitting on a curb, with your face in your hands, praying about what to do next
所以，想像你在托着你的脸想这个问题，祷告询问着撇下所有之后干啥，
and then these words come to mind
之后，这个话会进入你的脑海，
"Go into all the world and preach the gospel to everyone
“你们往普天下去，传福音给万民听”。
"teaching them to obey everything that I've just told you to do."
凡我所吩咐你们的，都教训他们遵守，
Does that sound like heading off into the wilderness to forge for food?
这听起来像是走进旷野去寻找食物吗？
Does it sound like planting vegetables and getting a milk cow?
这听起来像是种菜或者挤牛奶吗？
Does it sound like moving in with your parents and letting them feed you?
这听起来像是搬去和你父母住去啃老吗？
Or does it sound like going out and finding a new job so you can take care of your wife and kids?
或者这听起来像是出去找个新工作来照顾你的妻子孩子吗？
No, to all of these questions.
不，这些都不是。
It sounds like you already have a job, and you need to get busy doing it.
这听起来像是你已经有这个工作了，现在你需要忙起来做这个工作。
There are any number of ways
有许多的方法，
that you might try to get others to see and hear what you have seen and heard from Jesus.
你可以使用，来让别人看到听到你从耶稣所看到听到的。
And the more you listen to Jesus, the more you will be able to share with others, in one way or another.
并且，你听耶稣的话越多，你能够和人分享的也越多，通过某种方法或其他的方法。
One way could be to hire a hall and fill it with people, so you can stand up on the stage and preach to them.
一个方法是租个大厅，招满人来听，然后你可以站在舞台上向他们讲道。
Another might be to ask the local church to let you preach.
另一个方法或许是找个教会请他们许可你讲道。
Do you think you would be successful with either of them?
你认为你能用上面任一种方法获得成功吗？
Probably not.
或许并不能。
The local church, in particular, doesn't want to you in the teachings of Jesus
在教会里，尤其是教会，不会想让你教导耶稣的话。
we can be pretty sure of that.
我们很确信这一点。
And filling a hall with listeners
租个大厅招满人？
in a world where thousands of other voices are screaming for their attention every day
在这个世界上，有着千万种声音在吸引着人们的注意力，
can be a huge ask for most of us as well.
让人来听对大部分人是个艰巨的要求。
I know I've never been able to do either with much success.
我知道，我不能用上面的任何一种方法获得什么成功。
But you could do like Jesus: go out into the marketplaces and talk to people.
但是你可以像耶稣那样做：去到市场上去，对人们传讲。
That should get you up off the curb and on to your feet.
这会使你脱离压抑，走出去。
Shouting a sermon may work for a few people
大声的喊叫传道或许对一些人有用，
but I found that pretty difficult too, because today's world is just too busy
但我发现那个也相当的困难，因为今天的世界实在太忙了，
to stop and listen to a proper sermon.
人们根本没有时间停下来听道。
So, it kind of comes down to one on one witnessing to every creature.
所以，一对一的向每个被造物见证耶稣或许可行，
This works best in places where people are sitting down
当人们在坐着的时候，这个效果最好，
possibly with a few seconds that they can give to hearing what you have to say.
人们或许会给你几秒钟来听你必须说的话。
In parks, at bus stops, almost anywhere that you can find a bench or a table.
你可以这样在公园里，在公交站点，在每一个你可以找到凳子或桌子的地方。
You may need to show some interest in them to get started.
或许你要对他们表现的有兴趣来开始。
But approaching such people is definitely
a very good way to share the good news.
但是那样的靠近一些人，无疑是一个非常好的传福音的方法。
The more you talk to people,
the more you will learn just from experience
随着你向更多的人传讲，你会从你的经历中学到更多，
about how to get their attention and how to keep their interest
你也会学到如何获得人们的注意力并且让他们保持兴趣，
as you share the good news of Jesus with them.
就像你学会如何向他们分享耶稣的福音一样。
However, thanks to the modern media, we are now able to print up thousands of what we call 'tracts'
但是在今天，感谢现代的媒体，我们现在可以打印数千份的小册子，
which are just mini sermons on paper.
上面只写一些迷你讲道的内容。（注：简短讲道）
You can write and even illustrate your own tracks
and offer them to people.
你可以写下你自己的小册子，向人们展示，送给人们。
This has, by far, been the most proven and most successful way I've ever found to preach the gospel
这一个方法，在很长的时间里成为我们能找到的最有效的传福音的方法。
well, until I discovered YouTube.
直到有天，我发现了Youtube。
Through videos here on A Voice in the Desert, I've been able to reach over 300,000 people a month.
通过这些在“旷野之声”里的视频，每个月我能够触及到30万的人。
Nevertheless, even on the streets, you can offer these same videos, or others that you can make yourself
当然，就算在大街上，你也可以提供同样的视频，或者其他的你自己做的，
if you would prefer to do it that way,
to people everywhere
如果你愿意那样做的话，你可以在任何地方送给人，
just by getting a DVD replicator
to burn a hundred or more of them for you.
只需要有一个光盘复制器来烧录数百份或更多的光盘。
Wait a minute.
等一下。
How are you going to pay for all this material?
你打算怎样去为这些东西付款呢？
What I usually find is that even people who say they don't have anything to forsake
我经常发现的一件事情是，即使有些人说他们没有什么东西能撇下的，
actually do find they have enough possessions lying around to sell, and get maybe fifty dollars from them all.
但确实能发现他们有着许多东西在他们身边堆着，那些或许值个50美元。
That's enough to print up about a thousand little tracts or hundred DVDs and before you know it
那已经足够打印数千份小册子或者数百份光盘了，在不知不觉中，
you're out there preaching the gospel.
你已经正在传福音了。
Of course, if you don't even have $50,
you can still witness by word of mouth.
当然，即使你没有50美元，你仍然可以用你的口所说的话来见证耶稣。
Now, at this stage, you still don't know what you're going to do for breakfast, much less lunch
现在，在这个阶段，你仍然不知道如何搞到你的早饭，更不用说午饭了。
but remember, it's all about faith.
但是请记住，这些都关乎信心。
The important thing for us is to preach the gospel.
对我们来说重要的事情，是去传福音。
Jesus says, if we'll do the work he's given us to do,
he'll provide the food.
耶稣说，如果我们去做他要我们做的工作，他会提供食物。
Nevertheless, even if you're going to starve to death,
let's see how many thousands of people
再说了，即使你快要饿死了，我们却可以看到有那么多的人们，
we can witness to before we die.
听到了我们见证耶稣的福音。
Okay?
这足以。
I hope people are listening closely to what I'm saying here because
我希望人们能仔细的听我在这里说的，因为，
all this should be the natural flow on from forsaking all.
所有的这些是我们撇下一切后的很自然的走向。
You left your job, left your family, left the house,
the car, your education, your friends
and you're in the process of laying down your life for God.
Right?
But what are you going to do
as you slowly starve or freeze to death?
You are going to obey the rest of what Jesus said.
You're going to obey the great commission.
You're going to go into all the world,
or at least as much of it as you can reach
preaching the gospel to every person you see.
And here's when we come to an important crossroad.
I'm saying, and I think Jesus was saying, that once you start doing this
once you start seeking first to build God's Kingdom-- he's going to move in and take care of your spiritual needs.
And this is where the devil comes with quite a radically different way to stop YOU from serving God.
Up to this point, he would be saying,"No! no! Don't do it! You'll die! It won't work!
"You're tempting God! You've cracked up!"
Isn't that right?
Aren't those the thoughts that to keep coming into your head to challenge you on this?
But now, after you've started actually doing something
to share the gospel
he's going to takes a different approach.
Someone comes along--maybe another street person--and says, "You see that church over there?
"They give free clothes to street people in the hall next to the church, every Thursday."
Or someone will say, "There's a shelter just down the street where you can stay out of the cold tonight.
"Just go there before 7 p.m. and they'll give you a bed."
Or someone will say,
"You see that grocery store?
"In the bin behind the store are a hundred loaves of bread they threw out this morning
"you can eat your fill, for free"
Or someone will say, "Hey those little tracks (or DVDS) are quite good, but they must cost you money to print.
"Why don't you just ask people for a few cents to help pay for them?
"I'm sure most people would be happy to do that."
And what do you suppose the Devil is going to say?
"You can't do that. You're living by Faith!
"God will take care of you without you having to humble yourselves and accept handouts from other people."
"The gospel should be free; you can't ask for donations!"
"It's stealing to take bread from a supermarket rubbish bin!"
You see what I mean?
You've actually done what Jesus told you to do, and in the process you've met people.
These same people have shown you there's plenty of food, warmth, clothing, even money around
that is yours for the asking.
Are you too proud to ask?
Jesus said to his disciples, when he sent them out with nothing but the clothes on their backs
"When you enter a town, ask who in that town is worthy
"and then stay with them and accept what they give you."
Doesn't sound so unbelievably supernatural when you put it that way, does it?
And that seems to be one of the reasons why
so many people miss it.
You just get out there, and you do the hard yards and then God uses other people to meet your needs.
Sometimes it does look like handouts.
They don't know that they're feeding God's servants, and in many cases, if they did know, they might throw you out.
But God uses them anyway.
Other times it looks like you're back on a paid job.
You give them a tract, they give you ten cents.
But in fact, you're prepared to give it
for free, for as long as the tracts last.
It's just that they are doing what they do all the time
that is, giving you something to express their appreciation for what you have given them.
You feed them spiritually, and they feed you physically, even if it's only one cent that they give.
By the way, don't be afraid to refuse the donation
if it seems like the person giving it is not happy to be doing so.
We're not really selling the message, and we're not begging either.
We're just asking for free voluntary donations.
Is the picture starting to come together now?
Forsake all by all means, but don't stop there!
Go into all the world preaching the gospel.
If you have these two pieces to the puzzle,
you're well on your way.
A third piece is to work with other people.
You can learn more about that if you watch video number 5D in the 'Teachings of Jesus' playlist.
Follow those three steps, and I think you'll discover it's not nearly as hard as you thought it would be.
And it could be many years before you or your family ever get around to starving to death.
If you found this video helpful, please subscribe to this channel and click on the like button below.
Please share it with others, too.
And if you would like to get in touch with people who are living like this
please write to me at the address, which appears on the screen at the moment.
Tell me where you live and a little more about yourself when you write.
I look forward to hearing from you.